welcome to my youtube channel
jubilee creates something amazing by
meandering through life
because i invite you to do the same
start meandering
start doing what is yours to do doing
the next thing that calls to you
it doesn't need to look perfect all you
have to do is start
and create and that is what i am doing
this youtube channel unless somebody
else gets involved isn't gonna start
looking more professional
it's not gonna i'm not editing the
videos i don't
have the time energy to learn that and
do that
the capacity what i do have the capacity
to
is show up as i am learn the next thing
find the next thing that is mine to
learn and do
and keep doing it
and it is already unfolding on this
channel solution raisings
are a powerful tool that we can use to
create a world that works for us lives
that work for us
together tech is its own youtube channel
now
with even less subscribers than this one
but we are
coming together and creating the
technology and the tools that we need
a better world's on its way and we all
get to participate in co-creating it
together and if you have found this
video if you have found this youtube
channel
and this calls to you there's something
here
you found this for a reason like
subscribe hit the bell
because we are going to create a world
that works for you
for being for everyone and we are going
to do it
in a brand new way a way that isn't
about one influencer
having the audience it's about
everyone's voice being heard getting to
show up as yourself having permission to
make mistakes
on the way to getting it right and i'm
gonna
help you get there by showcasing all of
mine along the way
it's up it's down but i am profoundly
grateful to get to live this life and
share it with you
welcome